<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="x_nuvo_diag_probes">
    <x_nuvo_diag_probes action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <description>If you modify an existing Asset so that it should no longer meet the Asset Condition of a Scheduled Maintenance Definition (SMD), the asset will still be considered a match for the SMD until after the next scheduled recurrence of that SMD</description>
        <healthcheck_type/>
        <name>Updating or changing asset on SM</name>
        <order>100</order>
        <probe_type display_value="Facilities Maintenance">218325951b609510ae5b21b5ec4bcb45</probe_type>
        <product_version/>
        <remediation>Scheduled maintenance does not automatically recalculate which definitions apply to it on change of an asset record.&#13;
&#13;
It does a basic "try to find the best definition for me" logic on insert, and then it has some turning on and off maintenance instances based on the device status going in and out of retired/inactive install/active</remediation>
        <script><![CDATA[var util = new x_nuvo_diag.DiagnosticUtil();

util.handleOutput("If you modify an existing Asset so that it should no longer meet the Asset Condition of a Scheduled Maintenance Definition (SMD), the asset will still be considered a match for the SMD until after the next scheduled recurrence of that SMD. Scheduled maintenance does not automatically recalculate which definitions apply to it on change of an asset record. It does some basic -try to find the best definition for me- logic on the initial insert, and then it has some turning on and off of maintenance instances based on the device status going in and out of retired/inactive install/active.", 'Information','Facilities Maintenance');]]></script>
        <sys_class_name>x_nuvo_diag_probes</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>Harshal.Sonawane@nuvolo.com</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2022-08-02 11:27:15</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>4b399739db8ddd105f598b05059619a2</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>7</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>Updating or changing asset on SM</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Diagnostic Tool" source="x_nuvo_diag">3acdaefd1be7fc107798a9b7624bcb74</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Diagnostic Tool">3acdaefd1be7fc107798a9b7624bcb74</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>x_nuvo_diag_probes_4b399739db8ddd105f598b05059619a2</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>Stefan.Popov@nuvolo.com</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2024-09-17 11:21:27</sys_updated_on>
        <tool>diagnostic</tool>
    </x_nuvo_diag_probes>
</record_update>
